cerasis.com 2016-11-25

# Privacy Policy - Transportation Management Company | Cerasis

### Cerasis® Privacy Policy

This Cerasis® Privacy Policy (this or the “Privacy Policy”) explains our practices, defines our users’ (“you” or “your”) privacy options and describes how your information is collected and used by Cerasis, Inc. (“we,” “us,” “our,” or “Cerasis”).

By using the Cerasis® website or any of our applications, products, services, features, tools, or resources you agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy and our Terms of Use.

We reserve the right to modify this policy from time to time and will mark new versions with a corresponding effective date. We recommend you visit the Site to review any changes in our practices.

This Privacy Policy, along with our [Terms of Use](http://cerasis.com/cerasis-terms-service/), governs your use of the Cerasis® website at http://cerasis.com/ (“Site”), Cerasis® Rater®, and any other links through social media platforms such as Facebook or Twitter, as well as the use of our mobile application, Cerasis® mobile TMS. For the purposes of this Privacy Policy, we will refer to all of these access points as the Cerasis® system (“System”).

Our Site may contain links to other websites. These websites may have privacy policies different than our Privacy Policy. The Site may also contain certain social media icons or widgets. Although you can view the material we have linked to, you may have to create an individual account or register to use these third party social media sites to use interactive features. Any interaction on social media websites is governed by the terms of use and privacy policy of the particular platform.

#### What Information is Collected?

We may collect personal information from you on our Site or through any other digital or personal communication with you in the System. Information collected by us is voluntarily provided by you and may include information such as your name, email address, phone number, and physical address. Our Site may also collect general information about your technology interface or preferences (such as the type of browser used or the files requested). Additionally, we may collect information regarding the websites you visit and other information, as described in this Privacy Policy.

The information we may collect includes, but may not be limited to:

Your contact information to register to receive our newsletter and other company related updates, promotions and materials from us, such as your first name, last name, phone number, and email address;

Your transaction history relating to the use of our products and services;

Information regarding your browser and other technical specifications required to use our Site;

Computer data or files, often called “cookies,” which may be sent by your web browser and stored on an individual computer to allow our server to “recognize” you through the navigation of the Site and for us to credit your account for various online transactions;

Computer data files, often called “web beacons” that are collected from emails or links on third-party sites that allow our server to evaluate the popularity of those links or the information contained in emails or on third-party sites; and

Your IP address to measure our website traffic and to help provide a more personalized experience.

#### Children Under the Age of 13

Our Site and System are not designed for children and we do not knowingly collect information from any person we know is under the age of 13.

#### How is User Information Used and Shared?

We collect information about you in order to provide you with services and products and also collect information that is necessary for our Site to work properly. We use personal information about our users for a variety of purposes related to our business, including but not limited to:

Allowing you to receive information from us regarding Cerasis® products or services;

Tracking information about your visits to our Site to allow us to provide better service;

Using certain online preferences in the aggregate across all users to evaluate our Site and develop additional products and services to offer;

Sending or initiating direct marketing programs, such as newsletters or information about new products or services we are offering;

Contacting you regarding an inquiry on our Site that you have initiated;

If developed, using content from social media platforms where you discuss our products or use a hashtag related to our products;

Providing information about your usage or preferences to our third-party vendors and providers; and

Other purposes necessary to carry out our obligations under this Privacy Policy or our Terms of Use.

We may share information, in the aggregate, regarding your online browsing preferences to evaluate our products or allow third parties we work with to better serve our users. We will not share personally identifiable information in these instances, other than described in this Privacy Policy.

We may provide user information to third-party service providers or vendors for purposes of, including without limitation, initiating direct marketing programs on our behalf, data tracking, maintenance or development of our System, development of online products and services or customer service or new product development, or other contracted promotional opportunities provided to our users. We will not share your information with third parties to directly market their products to you. We may share this information with any subsidiaries, licensees, suppliers, distributors, affiliates, assigns, successors, or other related entities and their respective owners. We may also share your personal information in connection with law enforcement requests or in response to investigations, subpoenas, court orders, or other legal process to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims or as otherwise required by law.

#### Behavioral Advertising

We may also use third-party vendors, such as Google Analytics, to advertise to our users online. These third-party vendors may display Cerasis® product advertisements on other websites based on your internet usage. More specifically, these vendors use first-party cookies (such as the Google Analytic cookie) and third-party cookies (such as the DoubleClick cookie) together to inform, optimize, and serve ads based on your past visits to the Site or another site affiliated with Cerasis® products or services. Any information that these third parties collect via cookies is not linked to any personally identifiable information (name, address, email address, or phone number) we collect or you provide on the website. You can opt-out of Google Analytics for Display Advertising by using Google’s Ads Settings.

#### How is User Information Protected?

We maintain administrative, physical, and technical safeguards for all user information collected in our System.

#### How Can Users Limit Information Collected?

By providing information to us or browsing our Site, you are consenting to our use of your data as outlined in this Privacy Policy.

While we work hard to use and disclose our users’ personal information only for the purposes identified above, you can choose not to provide personal information or limit the personal information obtained by us as follows:

You may have your contact information removed from our marketing lists that are used to inform users of new or relevant products, services, and special offers by clicking on the unsubscribe link in any communication received from us or by emailing us at concerns@cerasis.com.

You may limit the collection of “cookies” from your Site usage through your browser settings. However, this may disable our ability to provide you with the most relevant products or information regarding the System; and

You may limit the ability of Google Analytics to track your online activity, as outlined in the “Behavioral Advertising” section.

#### Your California Privacy Rights

California Civil Code Section § 1798.83 permits users of our Site that are California residents to request certain information regarding our disclosure of personal information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes. To make such a request, please contact us via the Site.

#### Contacting Us

For additional information pertaining to our Privacy Policy, please contact:  
Cerasis, Inc.  
PO Box 21248  
Eagan, MN 55121  
800-734-5351
